vector.me 2018-12-26

# Privacy Policy - Vector.me

Vector.me knows that you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy very seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. By visiting the Vector.me website, you are accepting the practices outlined in this Privacy Policy. 

## Information Collected by Vector.me

We receive and store any information you enter on our website or provide to us in any other way. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of many of our special features. Generally, registration is not required to use Vector.me, but in order for you to use some services, such as adding icons to your favorite box, submitting new tags to icons, you must complete a registration form. As part of this registration form, we require select personal information (including your full name and e-mail address). We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. We receive and record certain "traffic data" on their server logs from your browser including your IP address, and the page you requested. We this traffic data to help diagnose problems with its servers, analyze trends and administer the website. We may collect and, on any page, display the total counts that page has been viewed. This includes User Profile pages. 

## E-mail Communications

We are very concerned about your privacy and will never provide your email address to a third party without your explicit permission. We only send out e-mails with product-related if you accept to receive them, as detailed in your account page. However, please note that in all cases you will continue to receive all system e-mails (e.g. those regarding forgotten user passwords) and legal notices (e.g. updates to our policies) from us. 

## Cookies

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and tell us how and when pages in our website are visited and by how many people. Vector.me cookies do not collect personal information, and we do not combine information collected through cookies with other personal information to tell us who you are or what your screen name or e-mail address is. 

## Keeping Information Secure

Your Vector.me account information is protected by a password for your privacy and security. Protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer by logging off once you have finished using a shared computer. Only our staff who need personal information to perform a specific job are granted access to it. All of our staffs are kept up to date on our privacy and security practices. 

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time, at its sole discretion. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes to the Privacy Policy, we will notify you by posting an announcement on the Vector.me website so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances if any, it is disclosed. 

## Conditions of Use

If you decide to visit Vector.me website, your visit and any possible dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Service, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of California state law. 

## Effective Date of this Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy is effective as of March 1, 2012.
